Number 6, how do you know that you are a
special person? That it's
meditation number six. How do you know that you are
special? That you
are a special person? Because you know
that you have the diamonds, or you know that you have
encountered the heart or in this life. You have encountered the Diamond
Cutter Sutra in this life.
Therefore, you must be very special
because you created it. You created the
Diermann Cutter Sutter, the heart or
created it. You can never go home again.
I am a special person. I
am not a particularly good person. I am
always sad and have no time. It has to be,
and I always have fears. He says it was,
but you are also special. You
created Buddhism on this planet. You created the Diamond Cutter.
You created the heart vehicle. You created
these eggs. You created
your mountain. Everything comes from
the, so appreciate yourself too. This is
meditation number 6, the fruits of the
visit. That is the name of meditation
number 6.
We do not live in a time where we
can meet the historical butter.
There, the robot has left this world,
but we  can enjoy the fruits of his
visit.
We have the heart. We have that
the man Schneider Sutter.
We have an unbroken line of
tradition for two and a half thousand
years.
Every two weeks, we recite,
defined as part of an unbroken line.
The teachers are there, the line is
unbroken.
You are the next, the next link in
an unbroken chain. He pleases
you a little about yourselves. The
visitors, the fruits of the visit, are the
fact that you have the heart, or hate the
fact that the man
Schneider Sutter has in your world.
The fruits of the visit are the bishop's understanding that Buddha
visited this world. Understood, proof
that we are blessed. The
proof that we are blessed.
You understand number five is that you
understand that his jewel is and
number six is ​​where you understand that you
have enough chambers. That in a world
with Buddhism still
living,
these two meditations are there so
that you are happy about yourself and your
life. So do these two
meditations really well.
When you get out, you should really
force yourself to be cool, and
immediately be happy about your life.
Only one in a million beings can
read the Heartzola, and it's very, very rare
in this universe.
You are at the top of the food chain,
the drummer chain. You have all these
teachings, you have the pen, you have the
four steps. You are extremely special
in this universe.
You are the most special people in
this universe. If Meditation 56 is
successful, then you should
wake up and have lunch with the
thought, "I am pretty cool."
You should be happy.